#### **Candidate Resume**

## Miguel Vega

Job\_title : PTA position location : Plant City, FL

Email: MiguelVegaPTA@Yahoo.com

Mobile : 813-730-9505 Date of Birth : N/A

# **Summary**

Motivated and caring Physical Therapist Assistant with over 25 years of experience providing quality patient care in various settings. Calm and reassuring personality, with strong communication abilities. Seeking a PTA position with a staff that emphasizes patient health and excellence, where I am able to apply my education, past experiences, and gain knowledge in our respected field.

## **Education**

School/College: Suffolk County Community College Course Name: A.A.S - Physical Therapist Assistant

Years: N/A

## **Skills**

Well-organized

**Detail Oriented** 

**Excellent Communication Skills** 

Bilingual (Spanish)

Flexible in working with Pediatric

Adolescent

Adult

and Geriatric Patients

#### **Work Experience**

**Position: PTA-Home Care** 

Company: Visitry Years: 2022-Domain: N/A

<u>Position: Rideshare Driver</u> Company: Self-Employed

Years: 2022 Domain: N/A

**Position: Functional Technician** 

Company: Functional Evaluation Testing of Florida

Years: 2016-2020 Domain: N/A

Position: PTA - Skilled Nursing / Rehab. Facility

Company: Total Healthcare Staffing

Years: 2015-2016 Domain: N/A

**Position: PTA - Outpatient Facility** 

Company: Orlin and Cohen Orthopedic Associates

Years: 2015 Domain: N/A

Position: PTA - Skilled Nursing / Rehab. Facility

Company: Tender Touch Rehab Services

Years: 2013-2015 Domain: N/A

Position: PTA - Skilled Nursing / Rehab. Facility

Company: Rehab Alternatives

Years: 2012-2013 Domain: N/A

**Position: PTA - Outpatient Facility** 

Company: CBC Center for Sports and Physical Therapy

Years: 1990-2011 Domain: N/A

## **Interests**

N/A

# **Speaking Languages**

Bilingual (Spanish)

#### **Certificates**

Licensed Physical Therapist Assistant - NY and FL Current Certification of Healthcare - CPR / AED / BLS

## **Achievements**

N/A

# **Projects List**

N/A

## **Years Of Experience:**

25

Current_position:	Current company:
N/A	N/A
Current company domain:	Current_company_business:
N/A	N/A
Previous_company:	Previous domain worked history:
N/A	N/A
Work authorization:	Clearance:
N/A	N/A
<u>Address</u>	
N/A	
Disability:	Patents info:
N/A	N/A
Primary Skills	
N/A	
extra_activities	
N/A	
Job_title	
N/A	
<u>city:</u>	state:
Plant City	FL
social media id:	<u>Linkedin_url:</u>
N/A	N/A